Curriculum Vitae

Aiden Taylor

Calgary, AB

Phone: (403)305-3001

Email: aiden.taylor1@ucalgary.ca

Research Interests

My research interests mainly lie in Pure and Applied Mathematical Analysis, as well as Computer Science, and I am specifically interested in Finite Element Methods. This includes the study of Adaptive Finite Element Methods, Mesh Generation Techniques, Functional Analysis, Operator Theory, Measure Theory, etc....

Education

09/2019 - 12/2023 University of Calgary

Degree: B.Sc. in Computer Science Concentration: Information Security

Minor: Mathematics

Academic Awards and Scholarships

09/2020 - 09/2022 Jason Lang Scholarships

Description: Have achieved a minimum Grade Point Average of 3.2 on a 4.0 point scale based on an 80% full course load in the previous fall

and winter terms.

05/2023 - 08/2023 NSERC USRA

Description: The Undergraduate Student Research Awards (USRA) program financially supports undergraduate research for more than 3,000 students annually. To be eligible to apply one must have obtained, over the previous years of study, a satisfactory cumulative average (normally at least a 3.0 on a 4.0 point scale).

Research Experience

05/2023 - 08/2023 NSERC-funded Undergraduate Research

Research topic: A Study of Function Spaces, and Adaptive Finite Ele-

ment Methods

Supervisor: Assoc. Prof. Cristian Rios

Work Experience

05/2021 - 08/2024 Canada Revenue Agency

Job title: Student Infrastructure Support Analyst

Description: My duties include providing technical advice to co-workers and clients, investigating and resolving hardware and software issues, taking inventory of hardware and software assets, and managing user

accounts, assets, and permissions.

References

These persons are familiar with my professional qualifications and my character:

Assoc. Prof. Cristian Rios

Organization: University of Calgary

Phone: (403)220-3221 Email: crios@ucalgary.ca